[Music] It has
happened
[Music]
Hello friends, welcome to the Option Gyan channel.
Friends, the
stock I am talking about today in Position Talkies is
called Metro Police. Friends, this stock has been
preparing to break the 3000 level for many days
but repeatedly fails in the green test.
Its land of Karo is the second T-20 line,
hence it tries to cross it
again and again but fails in the external attempt. So
it is preparing again. If it
stands above 3000 for a day or two, then you will soon
see the target of 3038.
Friends, you can consider this topic
for both positional and long term.
If you are participating in a position, then
you should bike it here
or around it.
And if this topic stands below 350 for
a day or two, then you have to edit your position.
But those who are
watching it from Investment for Interview,
they have to
invest only 30% of their capital here,
8085, the
remaining 30% you have to invest
80  You have to invest around Rs. 1000
and the remaining money that you have to invest friends,
40% of this money will be
around Rs. 14230, in
this way you have to invest to such an extent
that why I am talking about investing in ambulance, for that
you have to
look at its fundamentals, for
this position I have told you that you have to
like 2008, if you stand for a day or two at August 2002, then
very soon you will see a cut of 336
or you will get like 10 or 15
cents of profit, take your profit,
but if you want to see the investment point
office, because the market is live
time, then it will definitely give a correction once, so
when there is a correction, you should
not panic, I have told you that you have to
invest around 2016, you have to
press one and secondly you have to
wish around 23,
now let us discuss it fundamentally,
we have decided that
this is ticket paper,
investment Chakli here  A develop point has been
created, in which
three out of four points are
seen surrounded, one point is that of the first
point of intrinsic value, although the
rate of which is friends, it is dominating, that
means there is a lot of movement, that is why the point is
seen arrested, the infection for digital is
showing Tata,
now if we talk about its pencil stand, then the
company has continuously increased its profit
and has increased its develop,
friends, the revenue of the company in 2018 has
almost increased by 80%
and the profit that the company had
in 2018, that profit fall is also going to happen almost
in 2021, the data is
of only six months, so if the
company still has six months more time, then it
can do well within the company,
next if we talk about the financial statement of the company, then the
financial statement of the company is also
looking quite good to you, these
three points are seen surrounded,
if we talk about the net income of the company
Friends, the net income of the company is
less than the industry setting of 300, the
net income of the industry is less than 806, friends, the net income of the channel is
806 and the profit of this company is around 90%, so
please subscribe, that is why I am talking about the parties, you must have liked this video and it will be very beneficial for you, with this I end the video, thank you friends, if you like this video then please do not forget to like, share and subscribe,
thank you for watching my video
[Music]